What are you doing?
Bringing your memory back.
Stop it.
- What are you two doing?
- Cha.
We're up here to look at
the architectural drawings.
Open it then. I'd love to see them too.
If she's the real Claire,
she'll have a scar on her back.
You're still up, Grandpa.
Let me talk to Chan for a bit.
I hope you haven't forgotten
the promise you made to me.
What are you hiding in there?
Let me see.
There's nothing about you in here.
If that's true,
why won't you let me see it?
- Let me see.
- I said it's nothing.
Are you hiding something else?
You must be hiding something from me.
- What are you doing? It's nothing.
- I don't care. Let me see.
- Hey.
Well...
I, NITCHAN SATHITPHONG, PROMISE THAT
I WILL ONLY MARRY KHAEDARUN KANCHATHARA.
This is...
You wanted to know so badly, right?
I'm sorry.
Let me ask you something.
What did you promise her grandfather?
I promised him I would protect
and take care of Claire with my life.
In that case, I'll get out of your hair.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I snapped at you.
I guess I was missing Claire.
Um, I...
I'm sorry too.
I didn't know you were missing her.
Chan? Chan.
Uh, sorry.
I can come back.
Oh, I'm just leaving.
Hope I'm not interrupting.
If Ms. Claire were still alive,
you would've married her by now.
I'm sorry I snapped at you.
I guess I was missing Claire.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
I...
I was just lost in my thoughts.
What about you?
I followed you out here.
I want you to wear this bracelet.
Fine.
I'm telling you,
I'm accepting this bracelet
not because I'm softening up.
I just thought that if I were Ms. Claire,
she would've accepted it.
She wouldn't have cared.
Are you done?
Then I'm off.
Why is being Ms. Claire so exhausting?
Yes?
It's me.
What is it?
I...
I missed you.
Claire.
No.
I'm not Ms. Claire.
I know.
Well, then...
Tonight...
can you be her for me?
What do you mean?
Ms. Claire?
Excuse me?
Ms. Claire, excuse me?
Ms. Claire?
Yes?
There are people here
to see you at the pool.
Okay, I'll be right down.
Ms. Patch, Ms. Yo.
See? I told you
Ms. Claire wasn't mad at us.
What's going on?
The leak, of course.
Well...
We were worried,
so we wanted to clear things up with you.
With the leak, we thought you did it.
And you probably thought we did it.
But actually, there might be someone else
who wants to ruin all of us.
Exactly.
So we came up with the best way out.
How?
By becoming actual friends.
This way, people can't criticize you
for hiring us to be your friends.
How does that sound?
Well...
Okay.
Then we should celebrate our friendship.
Tonight?
Yes, tonight.
Oh, let's make it some other day.
Why, Ms. Claire?
Or are you still mad at us?
No, it's just that it's getting late.
Oh, Ms. Claire.
How is this late?
The night's still young.
It's going to be a long night. Please.
- Please come.
- Please.
- Come with us, Ms. Claire.
- Please, come.
Please, please, please.
Here, Ms. Claire,
right this way. Take it in.
Guys, look who's here!
- Ms. Claire!
- Hello!
- She's gorgeous.
- She's beautiful.
Look at her.
- Cheers!
Whoo!
- Ms. Claire...
- Wow, are you the real Ms. Claire?
Uh, yes.
Let me tell you, we've been
wanting to meet you for a long time.
Right, guys?
- Yes!
- Yeah!
Alright, why don't you sit here?
- Come on.
- What about you two?
Don't worry.
Yo and I need to take care of something.
We'll be right back.
Okay? Got, take care of her.
- You got it.
- Sit right here.
- Wait here.
- Take care of her, Got.
- You got it.
Uh, I'll go get you a drink, Ms. Claire.
No, thank you.
Just a little. I'll be back.
Ms. Claire, can I take a photo with you?
Sure.
You saw us, right?
I brought Ms. Claire like you wanted.
I did exactly what you wanted.
Give me Ms. Claire's contract.
Sure.
What's this?
You're so annoying.
Don't pretend you don't know these drugs.
You're already familiar
with them, aren't you?
Put this drug in Claire's drink.
Once she passes out, take her to a room.
After the job's done,
I'll give you the contract
and delete this video.
- What the hell are you doing?
- What's wrong?
You think I won't leak it? Try me.
Cha.
I think you've done enough.
What are you up to now?
You can see that's Claire.
But I don't believe it.
The real Claire has a scar on her back.
And what if she doesn't?
Then she's fake.
And what if she has the scar?
That's even better.
Because I've prepared
a lot of fun things for her.
Whether she's real or fake,
she won't survive tonight.
What are you up to now?
Chris, picture this.
Her passing out for just one night,
then waking up and finding out
she has three lovers all at once.
It's gonna be so much fun.
Here you go, Ms. Claire.
Oh, no, thank you. I'd rather not.
Come on, this is a party.
Have a drink to enjoy yourself.
Uh, in that case,
I'll just have plain water.
Come on now, Ms. Claire.
We're partying.
You can't have plain water.
Have this instead.
Orange juice,
perfect for an angel like you.
Okay, then.
Oh, wait.
Guys!
Today, Ms. Claire
agreed to be our friends.
So let's raise a glass to her!
Cheers!
Bottoms up.
Oh, just a little bit more.
- Oh.
- Please?
Okay.
Let's have fun.
Just a bit.
You should have told me
that you were coming,
so I could accommodate you better.
Get me at my office when you're done.
I think we should move
Ms. Claire's body to our hospital.
I don't trust this place.
Keep her here.
No one here knows Claire.
If anyone thinks of looking for her body,
no one would expect us to keep her here.
Uh, I think it's starting to get late.
I should head back.
Oh, no.
You can't, Ms. Claire.
You haven't even been here an hour.
Stay a bit longer.
Please, Ms. Claire.
Oh, please stay, Ms. Claire.
Oops. Ms. Claire?
What's wrong?
Sit, sit. You should sit down.
Why do I feel so dizzy?
Please sit down.
Are you okay?
Ms. Patch, what did you give me?
Orange juice.
You must be getting a contact high.
Don't worry.
I'll have my friend take you to rest.
- Got!
Take Ms. Claire to rest.
Let me take you, Ms. Claire.
Let's go, Ms. Claire.
Uh, I'm fine.
You're very drunk. You should rest.
- I'm fine. I'll figure it out...
- Let's go.
Get off me. Get off.
Get off me!
- Ms. Claire, stay with us, please.
- Let go.
Ow!
Ms. Claire?
Where are you, Ms. Claire?
We won't hurt you.
Come out.
Please come out.
Don't just stand there.
The door won't
open itself. Go find the key.
Go find the key.
I got the key.
Open it. Open it now.
Got it?
- Got it?
- Got it.
Search.
Ms. Claire?
- Where are you?
- Ms. Claire.
Where are you?
- Where the hell is she?
- Where are you?
Where is Claire?
She came into this room,
but she was gone once we got in.
The window.
It's open. She must've got out this way.
Claire?
Carry her to the bed.
Get out.
Hey.
What are you gonna do to me?
Nothing much.
I just want to check something.
But don't worry.
Because you won't remember anything
when you wake up.
Is it done?
Tell them to handle her,
film her and send me the video.
Cha.
Don't do this, Cha.
Why not?
Or you want to do it yourself?
Let's go, guys.
Man.
Wow.
I've always wondered how sweet
socialites taste.
So sweet, dudes. Here we go.
Let's see.
We should get some evidence, right?
Yeah, let's do it.
- Right?
- Do it, dude.
Who's next?
Film it for me too.
Yeah, you go next. I'll finish it off.
Is this a good idea, Patch?
You know who Ms. Claire is.
What are we supposed to do?
If we refuse, Ms. Cha will ruin us.
Let them do it
and send the video to Ms. Cha.
We'll delete it later.
Let me have a sniff.
- Where is Ms. Claire?
- Whoa.
I asked where she is.
What is it, Mom?
I came to ask you about Claire.
Have you figured out
if she's the real Claire?
But looking at you,
I think I've got my answer.
Think carefully
before you do anything next time.
Don't get carried away.
So what next?
Don't worry about that, Mom.
Your job is to do whatever it takes
to make Dad love and trust you again.
As for Claire, I'll handle her.
How?
Are you gonna tell your Dad
she isn't the real Claire
just because that stupid scanner
didn't recognize her face?
Do you think he'll believe you?
We can't prove it right now
whether she's real or an impostor,
but we can at least show Dad that
letting his no-good, troublemaker
grandchild return to run the company
will only bring disgrace to our business.
Last night, I watched a moral drama.
Claire was the protagonist.
It's called...
"The Wicked Grandchild
and Her Seven Lovers."
Wanna watch it?
SEND ME THE VIDEO WHEN IT'S DONE.
What?
Why isn't it here?
What isn't here?
PATCHY
Hey.
I told you last night to send me the video
after you handled Claire.
So did you handle her or not?
Cha! Hey!
What happened last night?
Can you not right now?
I told you I'd tell you later.
Hey.
Where are you going now?
You must be in a hurry to get rid of
the evidence from last night.
What evidence?
The evidence of you hiring people
to gang rape Claire.
What the hell are you doing?
Give it here. What are you trying to do?
What are you doing?
- Chan.
- What are you trying to do?
What are you trying to do?
Were you filming?
Get the hell out.
Get out!
Claire? Claire?
Claire? Can you hear me, Claire?
Claire?
What did you give her?
I don't know.
Ms. Cha gave it to me.
But I think it's a date rape drug.
It was Ms. Cha's order.
We had nothing to do with it.
Check the phone.
Delete all the videos of her.
You got it.
DELETE
Claire?
Claire? Claire?
Claire, can you hear me? Claire?
Claire?
Claire? Claire?
You've targeted Claire many times before.
But this time you've gone too far.
How do you know
it was me? Do you have proof?
My proof is the witness
who called me to rescue Claire.
Aren't you curious
how I knew where Claire was,
and how I saved her in time?
This is the last time I'll let it slide.
If something like this happens again,
I'll use the power the chairman
gave me to take decisive action.
Cha.
Tell me everything
that happened last night.
How did Chan find out?
Cha! Cha, come back here, Cha!
Cha!
Chris!
- Where's your phone?
- Why, Cha?
- What's wrong?
- Give me your phone.
Cha.
Cha. Hey, Cha.
Cha, why are you looking through my phone?
Cha.
RECENT OUTGOING CALLS
Will you tell me what's going on?
How did Chan save Claire last night?
- What?
- How did Chan know where Claire was?
Wait. Did you think I called him?
Why would I do that, Cha?
Because you're a dog in the manger.
You didn't wanna share her.
Cha.
You know I was with you all night.
When could I call Chan?
Maybe Chan had that bodyguard follow us.
Go get dressed.
Where are we going?
Well, if you want me to trust you,
you gotta prove yourself to me.
I never expected you to call me.
Mr. Chan, listen to me.
You need to save Ms. Claire.
I don't have time to explain.
Ms. Cha's having people gang rape her
and film a video to blackmail her.
I'll send you the location. I have to go.
You called to find out
if Ms. Claire's safe, right?
I know about that now.
Cha came to see me.
And she wanted to know who told you.
You don't have to worry.
I didn't tell her anything.
Where am I?
Why am I wearing this?
Hey.
You're awake.
Are you hungry? I made you breakfast.
How did I end up here?
Well, you passed out.
I brought you here
so the chairman wouldn't suspect anything.
Uh, and...
who changed my clothes?
Don't tell me...
You...
How could you do that to me?
Didn't want me to see?
Actually,
I've seen more than this.
Hey!
Have you forgotten that
the body standing in front of me
is the body I gave you?
If you're holding that over my head,
ask yourself if I even wanted
this body you gave me.
You claim you saved my life,
but you have no right
to violate my body like this.
Let's just say...
I didn't do anything inappropriate.
So,
what do you remember?
I...
remember Ms. Yo and Ms. Patch
taking me to someone's house.
Cheers!
And suddenly I felt drowsy
and groggy, and...
Uh, I'm fine.
You're very drunk.
- Let's go, Ms. Claire.
- Let go of me.
Get off me!
I remember men trying to assault me.
Ms. Cha tricked you into going there.
Ms. Cha tricked me?
Why would she do that?
She wanted to prove
if you are the real Claire.
How?
How would she know if I'm the real Claire?
Well...
The real Claire had a scar on her back.
What?
Now what are we going to do?
So Ms. Cha knows I'm not the real Claire.
If someone like Ms. Cha found out
you weren't the real Claire,
would she let you stay here?
What do you mean?
I don't have a scar on my back.
Why do I have a scar like Ms. Claire?
Didn't I tell you before?
I didn't make you look like Claire.
I made you be her.
And it's not just the scar.
You must be identical to her.
I would give you
a blood transfusion if I could.
But I'm not Ms. Claire.
My name is Jinla.
Hold on, hey.
- Hey. Hey...
- Let go. Let go.
- Listen to me.
- I said let go! Let go!
Hey, let me go! Let go!
I said let go!
What is this?
I asked what this is.
Why is it inside the bracelet you gave me?
Why is there a GPS?
You used me as bait.
You knew Ms. Cha was going
to do something like this to me.
Since the incident at the vault,
I knew Ms. Cha wondered
whether you were the real Claire.
And someone like her
would find a way to prove it.
What's going on?
Look, do whatever it takes
to get him here ASAP.
Tell him I'll pay extra.
The biometric scanner at the vault
detected that she isn't Ms. Claire.
And Ms. Cha knows about it?
Ms. Claire's doctor just called me.
Said Ms. Cha asked about
the scar on Ms. Claire's back.
A scar on her back?
So I figured Ms. Cha
would find a way to look at your back.
Until...
I saw Yo and Patchy show up.
See? I told you
Ms. Claire wasn't mad at us.
What's going on?
Then we should celebrate our friendship.
- Please, Ms. Claire.
- Let's go.
- Please.
- Please come with us.
- Let's go.
Please, please, please.
- Let's go, come on.
- Please.
- Yay, she says yes!
- Let's go.
- Come on.
How is it? Is the signal okay?
It's working properly.
But are you sure you want to do this?
Ms. Cha could hurt Ms. Jin.
We need Ms. Cha to see that scar
with her own eyes.
So I had to let them drug you
so she'd believe you are the real Claire.
Because the only one who can
make Ms. Cha stop doubting you
is Ms. Cha herself.
What the hell are you doing?
What are you trying to do?
What are you trying to do, huh?
Were you filming?
Claire? Claire?
But the plan went wrong because...
Claire?
I'd thought Ms. Cha would stop there.
I trusted you.
I've done everything you said.
But you turned me into a tool.
What else was I supposed to do?
Did you have another way?
You know when Ms. Cha suspects something,
she will stop at nothing.
I have a way to make everything stop.
I will tell everyone I'm not Ms. Claire.
My name is Jinla.
The woman
whose life you've turned into hell.
Just like that,
everything stops.
And do you think I'd let you do that?
Why not?
What are you gonna do?
Are you gonna kill me?
Or are you gonna make me disappear?
Go ahead.
Do it.
I know you won't dare.
Because if you do anything to me,
Ms. Claire will disappear too.
No, she won't.
I'll just find another woman
to replace you as Claire.
You're well aware.
The Kanchathara family
has enough money to buy anyone's life.
I'll just have to find...
another woman to replace you as Claire.
But let's not complicate things.
You're just angry right now.
Go home and calm down.
I'll handle the rest myself.
Oh, hey. Are you okay?
I'll just find another woman
to replace you as Claire.
I hate you!
I hate you. I hate you.
What happened?
Why did she look so angry?
It's nothing.
I just reminded her of her place.
So she knows.
What did you want?
Chan.
I think Ms. Claire was murdered.
What do you mean?
The police called
about the pilot's blood test.
They found GHB in his blood.
Sir?
Here is what you requested.
Thank you, Captain.
That pilot was really drugged.
I hate you.
I hate you! Do you hear me? I hate you!
Chan.
The day you dropped off Ms. Claire,
was there anything unusual?
Unusual?
Like what?
Like the pilot's demeanor or behavior.
Did he look dazed, or unwell, or anything?
Because GHB takes about
20 minutes to take effect.
So I need to know if the pilot showed
any symptoms before taking off.
Good morning, Captain.
Good morning.
It's a beautiful day.
Visibility should be great.
The sky is clear today.
I've been instructed to fly around
the project site with no landing, correct?
Yes. Let's wait and see
if Ms. Claire wants anything extra.
Alright. If you'll excuse me.
- Sure. Thank you.
- Sure.
I don't think so.
He looked perfectly normal to me.
Then how did GHB
end up in the pilot's blood?
Given the time for
the drug to take effect,
the pilot must have been drugged
before he boarded.
And the only one
who can tell us what happened is...
Ms. Jinla.
Why is the chairman at the office?
Is this about
Ms. Cha's suspicion about Ms. Jin?
The facial scanner outside the vault
suddenly didn't
recognize Claire's face, Dad.
You just won't stop, will you?
If you don't want
my dad to switch the project,
just bring Claire here now.
Can we open the door now?